{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871501650","data":{"timestamp":" 946871501650"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871501894","data":{"timestamp":" 946871501893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871502776","data":{"timestamp":" 946871502776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871503270","data":{"timestamp":" 946871503270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871503843","data":{"timestamp":" 946871503843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYUMBA"," userResponse":" VYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871504756","data":{"timestamp":" 946871504756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871505879","data":{"timestamp":" 946871505879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871506763","data":{"timestamp":" 946871506763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAANZA"," userResponse":" WANAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871507576","data":{"timestamp":" 946871507576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKUWA"," userResponse":" KUTOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871507848","data":{"timestamp":" 946871507848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871508632","data":{"timestamp":" 946871508632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871510636","data":{"timestamp":" 946871510636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871512205","data":{"timestamp":" 946871512205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871514340","data":{"timestamp":" 946871514340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871515790","data":{"timestamp":" 946871515790"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871517589","data":{"timestamp":" 946871517589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871519741","data":{"timestamp":" 946871519741"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871522123","data":{"timestamp":" 946871522123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871525314","data":{"timestamp":" 946871525314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871528001","data":{"timestamp":" 946871528001"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871530735","data":{"timestamp":" 946871530735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871533969","data":{"timestamp":" 946871533969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu wa kijiji cha vyumba vidogo walikuwa wanaanza kutokuwa na furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871535895","data":{"timestamp":" 946871535895"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871536089","data":{"timestamp":" 946871536089"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871536923","data":{"timestamp":" 946871536922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITUNI"," userResponse":" MWITUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871537755","data":{"timestamp":" 946871537755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" WALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871538409","data":{"timestamp":" 946871538409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871539031","data":{"timestamp":" 946871539031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871539595","data":{"timestamp":" 946871539595"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871540907","data":{"timestamp":" 946871540907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAOGOFYA"," userResponse":" KUWAOGOFYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871542686","data":{"timestamp":" 946871542686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871546450","data":{"timestamp":" 946871546449"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871549513","data":{"timestamp":" 946871549513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871551533","data":{"timestamp":" 946871551533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWITUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871557231","data":{"timestamp":" 946871557230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871562606","data":{"timestamp":" 946871562606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871564735","data":{"timestamp":" 946871564735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871567142","data":{"timestamp":" 946871567142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871569416","data":{"timestamp":" 946871569416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wa mwituni walianza kufika pale na kuwaogofya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAOGOFYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871571823","data":{"timestamp":" 946871571822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871572296","data":{"timestamp":" 946871572296"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871573165","data":{"timestamp":" 946871573165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKULA"," userResponse":" WALIKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871573844","data":{"timestamp":" 946871573843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMEA"," userResponse":" MIMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871574395","data":{"timestamp":" 946871574394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871574968","data":{"timestamp":" 946871574967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871578110","data":{"timestamp":" 946871578110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871580815","data":{"timestamp":" 946871580815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871583395","data":{"timestamp":" 946871583395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871587236","data":{"timestamp":" 946871587235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871590602","data":{"timestamp":" 946871590602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871592591","data":{"timestamp":" 946871592591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama hawa walikula mimea yao yote."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871594349","data":{"timestamp":" 946871594349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871595543","data":{"timestamp":" 946871595543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWABEBA"," userResponse":" WALIWABEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871596578","data":{"timestamp":" 946871596577"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871596801","data":{"timestamp":" 946871596801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871597914","data":{"timestamp":" 946871597914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAONDOSHA"," userResponse":" KUWAONDOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871598308","data":{"timestamp":" 946871598308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871601868","data":{"timestamp":" 946871601868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871604136","data":{"timestamp":" 946871604136"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWABEBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871606041","data":{"timestamp":" 946871606041"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871607952","data":{"timestamp":" 946871607951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871610437","data":{"timestamp":" 946871610437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAONDOSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871612468","data":{"timestamp":" 946871612468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata waliwabeba watoto na kuwaondosha pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871614837","data":{"timestamp":" 946871614836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871615521","data":{"timestamp":" 946871615520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871616286","data":{"timestamp":" 946871616285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAZURI"," userResponse":" PAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871616507","data":{"timestamp":" 946871616506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871617210","data":{"timestamp":" 946871617210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871617834","data":{"timestamp":" 946871617834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871621157","data":{"timestamp":" 946871621157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871623013","data":{"timestamp":" 946871623013"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871625257","data":{"timestamp":" 946871625256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871626782","data":{"timestamp":" 946871626782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871628842","data":{"timestamp":" 946871628841"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871630743","data":{"timestamp":" 946871630743"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapakuwa pahali pazuri pa kuishi tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871632664","data":{"timestamp":" 946871632664"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871633469","data":{"timestamp":" 946871633469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEENDA"," userResponse":" WANGEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871634391","data":{"timestamp":" 946871634391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871637890","data":{"timestamp":" 946871637890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871640772","data":{"timestamp":" 946871640771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGEENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871643793","data":{"timestamp":" 946871643793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini wangeenda wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871645447","data":{"timestamp":" 946871645447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" MIMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871646246","data":{"timestamp":" 946871646246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871646819","data":{"timestamp":" 946871646819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871647384","data":{"timestamp":" 946871647384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPATA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871647394","data":{"timestamp":" 946871647394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIBU"," userResponse":" ILIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871655035","data":{"timestamp":" 946871655034"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946871655123","data":{"timestamp":" 946871655123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000103_065121"," gameId":" 96b76d54-49ab-4eca-8d6a-cd4cefcaa08b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia moja ilipata jibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIBU"," userResponse":" ILIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}